<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PlayerListCustom30</string>
    <string name="bangladesh_short_details">
        Bangladesh is a country in Southern Asia . . .
    </string>
    <string name="bangladesh_long_details">
        Bangladesh is a country in Southern Asia and is located on the Bay of Bengal bordered by India on all sides except for a small border with Burma. Bangladesh has flat plains, and most of the country is situated on deltas of large rivers flowing from the Himalayas. The government system is parliamentary democracy; the chief of state is the president, and the head of government is the prime minister. Bangladesh has a traditional economic system in which the allocation of available resources is made on the basis of inheritance and primitive methods. Bangladesh is a member of the Asia-Pacific Trade Agreement (APTA) and the South Asian Association for Regional Cooperation (SAARC).
        Stretching northward from the Bay of Bengal, Bangladesh constitutes roughly the eastern two-thirds of the deltaic plain of the Padma (Ganges [Ganga]) and Jamuna (Brahmaputra) rivers. Except for small higher areas of jungle-covered old alluvium (rising to about 100 feet [30 metres]) in the northwest and north-centre—in the Barind and the Madhupur Tract, respectively—the plain is a flat surface of recent alluvium, having a gentle slope and an elevation of generally less than 30 feet (9 metres) above sea level. In the northeast and southeast—in the Sylhet and Chittagong Hills areas, respectively—the alluvial plains give place to ridges, running mainly north-south, that form part of the mountains that separate Bangladesh from Myanmar and India. In its southern region, Bangladesh is fringed by the Sundarbans, a huge expanse of marshy deltaic forest.
        The Barind is a somewhat elevated triangular wedge of land that lies between the floodplains of the upper Padma and Jamuna rivers in northwestern Bangladesh. A depression called the Bhar Basin extends southeast from the Barind for about 100 miles (160 km) to the confluence of the Padma and Jamuna. This area is inundated during the summer monsoon season, in some places to a depth exceeding 10 feet (3 metres). The drainage of the western part of the basin is centred in the vast marshy area called the Chalan wetlands, also known as Chalan Lake. The floodplains of the Jamuna, which lie north of the Bhar Basin and east of the Barind, stretch from the border with Assam in the north to the confluence of the Padma and Jamuna in the south. The area is dominated by the Jamuna, which frequently overflows its banks in devastating floods. South of the Bhar Basin is the floodplain of the lower Padma.

    </string>
    <string name="pakistan_short_details">
        Pakistan emerged on the world map  . . .
    </string>
    <string name="pakistan_long_deails">
        Pakistan emerged on the world map as an independent sovereign state in August 1947, as a result of the division of the British Indian Empire. With a land area of 881,913 sq. km. [including FATA (Federal Administered Tribal Areas) and FANA (Federal Administered Northern Areas)], its population stands at nearly 172.80 million, according to the 2008 Census. Historically, this is one of the most ancient lands known to man. Its cities flourished before Babylon was built; its people practiced the art of good living and citizenship before the celebrated ancient Greeks.

The region traces its history back to at least 2,500 years before Christ, when a highly developed civilization flourished in the Indus Valley. Excavations at Harappa, Mohenjodaro and Kot Diji have brought to light evidence of an advanced civilization flourishing here even in most ancient times. Around 1,500 B.C. the Aryans conquered this region and slowly pushed the Hindu inhabitants further east, towards the Ganges Valley. Later, the Persians occupied the northern regions in 5th century B.C. The Greeks came in 327 B.C., under Alexander of Macedonia, and ran through the region like a meteor. In 712 A.D. the Arabs, led by Mohammed Bin Qasim, landed somewhere near what is now Karachi, and ruled the lower half of Pakistan for two hundred years. During this time Islam took root and influenced the life, culture and traditions of the inhabitants of the region.

From 10th century A.D. onwards, a systematic conquest of Indo-Pakistan by the Muslims from Central Asia began and lasted up to 18th century A.D., when the British colonized the Sub-continent and ruled for nearly 200 years (for 100 years over what is now Pakistan). The Muslim revival began towards the end of the last century when Sir Syed Ahmed Khan, a renowned leader and educationist, launched a movement for intellectual renaissance of the Indian Muslims. In 1930, the well-known poet/philosopher, Dr. Mohammed Iqbal conceived the idea of a separate state for the Muslims of the Sub-continent, and in 1940, the All-India Muslim League adopted the famous Pakistan Resolution.

After seven years of untiring struggle, under the brilliant leadership of Quaid-e-Azam Mohammed Ali Jinnah, Pakistan emerged on the world map as a sovereign state on August 14, 1947, when the British Indian Empire was partitioned into two independent states – India and Pakistan.
    </string>
    <string name="india_short_details">
        India has the second-highest cases of global . . .
    </string>
    <string name="india_long_detials">
        India has the second-highest cases of global COVID-19 infections. USAID support has helped India strengthen health system resilience, readiness, response capacity, address stigma, and mobilize innovative financing mechanisms for emergency preparedness and response to the pandemic. USAID also helped India to address bottlenecks at different stages of the supply chain for HIV, TB, contraceptive, and other critical healthcare drugs and equipment, which are vital both for India and the world given that India’s pharmaceutical industry supplies 80 percent of the world’s medicines.

High rates of child and maternal death, widespread malnutrition, and persistently high TB and HIV rates threaten the lives and productivity of India’s expanding population. Exacerbating India’s health challenges, access to clean water and functioning toilets escapes about 40 percent of the population—making India home to the world’s highest number of diarrhea-related deaths in children under 5. USAID leverages Indian resources to strengthen the reach, affordability and quality of health care services. Also, with USAID support, since 2014, India has declared more than 4,000 cities open defecation-free, reducing the potential for health hazards.
    </string>
    <string name="korea_short_details">
        Korea’s dense urban centers, developed . . .
    </string>
    <string name="kores_long_details">
        Korea’s dense urban centers, developed parks and recreation facilities, high tech infrastructure and ultra modern public transportation systems are just some of the things that have made Korea a recognized hotspot for international business and travel. Seoul Olympic Park, located in the capital city of Seoul, preserves the spirit of the 1988 Summer Olympics and is open all day providing multipurpose areas for sports, leisure and a variety of cultural activities.

To this day, South Korea remains one of the world’s most ethnically homogenous countries. It is believed that the people of South Korea are direct descendants of several migratory Mongol tribes who ventured into the Korean Peninsula about a half million years ago. Today South Korea is home to approximately 49 million people making it one of the most densely populated countries in the world. South Korea currently maintains diplomatic relationships with over 170 different nations.
    </string>
    <string name="canada_short_details">
         Canada has two national languages, French . . .
    </string>
    <string name="canada_long_details">
        Canada has two national languages, French and English. This goes back to the initial settlers over 500 years ago, where both Britain and France formed colonies in the region. Canada remains part of the Commonwealth, the group of countries that were once part of the British empire.

Canada is a representative democracy, with Canadians voting to elect their representatives to the House of Commons, situated in Ottawa. Canada remains a constitutional monarchy, and still hold the British Monarch as Sovereign Head of State, although this is a purely ceremonial role without any political power.

Canadians are, in general, enthusiastic about sport, ice Hockey being the most popular, both in how many participate, and how many watch the professional teams. However, the national sport is actually Lacrosse, a sport that many will not have heard of, played with sticks that have nets fastened to the ends, and rubber balls.

Maple Syrup, drawn from the sap of Maple trees, is one of Canada’s most known food treats, along with poutine, which features French fries, cheese curds, and beef gravy. Poutine originated in Quebec but is a treat enjoyed by Canadians right across the country today.
    </string>
    <string name="croatia_short_details">
        Croatias media enjoy a high degree of independence . . .
    </string>
    <string name="croatia_long_details">
        Croatias media enjoy a high degree of independence. Croatian Radio-TV, HRT, is the state-owned public broadcaster and is financed by advertising and a licence fee.

Public TV is still the main source of news and information, but HRT is losing audience share and privately-owned Nova TV is now the top station.

National commercial networks and dozens of private local TV stations compete for viewers. The cable and satellite market is well developed.

There are three national public radio networks, four national commercial channels, regional public radios and more than 130 local and regional radios.

In the newspaper sector, there are six national and four regional dailies. Austrian and German concerns have large stakes in the print media.
    </string>
    <string name="finland_short_details">
        Finland (Finnish: Suomi) is a country . . .
    </string>
    <string name="finland_long_datails">
        Finland (Finnish: Suomi) is a country in Northern Europe and is a member state of the European Union. Finland is one of the Nordic countries and is also part of Fennoscandia. Finland is located between the 60th and 70th latitudes North. Its neighbours are Sweden to the west, Norway to the north, Russia to the east and Estonia to the south, beyond the sea called Gulf of Finland. Most of western and southern coast is on the shore of the Baltic Sea.

The capital of Finland is Helsinki; the second largest city is Tampere. The official currency of the country is the euro (EUR); before 2002 it was the markka, the Finnish mark (FIM). The president of Finland is Sauli Niinistö. 5.5 million people live in Finland. Finnish and Swedish both are the official languages of Finland; the most spoken languages is Finnish, mother tongue of about 90% of the population. Swedish is spoken by the Swedish speaking minority of Finland, called the Finnish Swedes, who make up 5% of the total population. Finland became independent of Russia on 6 December 1917.

The most important cities and towns in Finland are Helsinki, Espoo, Tampere, Vantaa, Turku, Oulu, Lahti, Kuopio, Jyväskylä and Pori.

Finland is a highly industrialised First World country. The most important Finnish industrial products are paper, and steel products such as machines and electronics. Nokia (the mobile company) is originally a company of Finland, named after a small town called Nokia.

Finland has been top of the list of least corrupt countries on the Corruption Perceptions Index more times than any other country.
    </string>
    <string name="argentina_short_details">
        Argentinas landscape is dominated by the Andean . . .
    </string>
    <string name="argentina_long_details">
        Argentinas landscape is dominated by the Andean mountains in the west; it is bounded by the South Atlantic Ocean in the southeast and the south. The country borders Chile to the west and the south, Bolivia and Paraguay to the north, Brazil to the northeast and Uruguay to the east. The country shares maritime borders with the Falkland Islands, a United Kingdom Overseas Territory.

Argentina has a population of 46 million people (2022 census); the capital and largest city is Buenos Aires. Official language is Spanish. English, Italian, German and French are spoken in the respective communities.

The term "Argentina" is derived from the Latin word "argentum," meaning silver. It refers to the early Spanish explorers belief that the region contained vast amounts of silver.

Geographical regions of Argentina
There are seven geographical regions in Argentina: Argentine Northwest; the Chaco Region (Gran Chaco), a hot and semi-arid lowland; the mountain chain of the Sierras Pampeanas; subtropical Mesopotamia (Littoral); Cuyo in central-west; the Pampas, a vast fertile alluvial plain; and Patagonia, the sparsely populated south of Argentina. The country offers several climatic zones ranging from (north to south) tropical and subtropical zones along the Brazilian border to temperate regions in the center to a subpolar area in the extreme south.
Due to its location in the Southern Hemisphere, the Argentine summer lasts from December to February.
    </string>
    <string name="brazil_short_details">
         Long known for the natural wonders . . .
    </string>
    <string name="brazil_long_details">
        Long known for the natural wonders of the Amazon rainforest and a vibrant culture that prizes living in the moment, Brazil has emerged as a powerful economic force in Latin America and the world economy befitting its status as one of the four original BRIC countries. Fueled by decades of healthy economic growth, Brazil overtook the U.K. in 2011 to become the world’s sixth largest economy. From 1980 to 2011, Brazil’s Human Development Index (HDI) increased by 30.8 percent.

Brazil is the world’s fifth largest country by both population and total area. The country’s great natural beauty and biodiversity is on display from the northern cities of Fortaleza and Manaus in the Amazon rainforest to Porto Allegre in the south. The breathtakingly picturesque, cosmopolitan coastal city of Rio de Janeiro vies with business-driven Sao Paulo as leading hubs of Brazil’s economic dynamism.

Several high profile, international events have recently contributed to Brazil’s growing presence on the world stage.  In 2014, Brazil celebrated its heritage of stylish soccer (football) in the FIFA World Cup. In 2016, Rio de Janeiro will show off its wares as the host city for the 2016 Summer Olympics.
    </string>
    <string name="bhutan_short_details">
        Bhutan occupies an area of 38,394 km² making . . .
    </string>
    <string name="bhutan_long_details">
        Bhutan occupies an area of 38,394 km² making it somewhat smaller than Switzerland or about half the size of the US state of Indiana. Bhutans landscape is mostly mountainous with some fertile valleys and savanna.

The country has a multiethnic population of 760,000 inhabitants (in 2015). There are three main ethnic groups in Bhutan, the Tshanglas (or Sharchop) are considered the aboriginal inhabitants of eastern Bhutan, the Ngalops, people of Tibetan origin who migrated to Bhutan, and the Lhotshampas, a group of Nepali language-speaking Bhutanese people. Official language is Dzongkha, a language closely related to Tibetan and Nepali. Capital and largest city is Thimphu.
    </string>
    <string name="indonesia_short_details">
        The entire country lies in the southwestern . . .
    </string>
    <string name="indonesia_long_details">
        The entire country lies in the southwestern arm of the "Ring of Fire," an extensive arc-shaped zone of prevalent volcanic activity, ocean trenches, fault lines, and plate movements that roughly parallels the coasts of the Pacific Ocean.
The islands of Indonesia are prone to earthquakes and even tsunamis. The island nation ranks third among countries with the most volcanoes, behind the US and Russia.

With an area of 1,904,569 km², Indonesia is the largest country consisting only of islands. The combined area of the archipelago is slightly smaller than Mexico or larger than five times the size of Germany.

The multi-ethnic country has a population of more than 271 million people (in 2021). It is by far the most populous island nation in the world. There are more than 1,300 recognized ethnic groups in Indonesia. The six largest ethnic groups are Javanese (40%), Sundanese (16%), Batak (4%), Sulawesi (3%), Madurese (3%) and Betawi (3%). [2]

The capital and largest city is Jakarta on the island of Java (pop. 10 million); other major cities are Bandung, Medan, Surabaya. The official language is Indonesian (Bahasa Indonesia). The main religion is Islam; almost nine-tenths of the Indonesian population are Muslims, the majority are Sunnis.
    </string>
    <string name="portugal_short_details">
        Portugal, officially The Portuguese Republic . . .
    </string>
    <string name="portugal_long_details">
        Portugal, officially The Portuguese Republic, is a country in southern Europe, founded in 1143, occupying a total area of 92,212 km2. The mainland is located on the southwest of the Iberian Peninsula, bordering Spain to the north and east, and the Atlantic Ocean to the west and south. The Portuguese territory includes two autonomous regions: the archipelagos of Madeira and Azores, in the Atlantic Ocean. The archipelago of Madeira is formed by the islands of Madeira and Porto Santo, and the island groups of Desertas and Selvagens; the archipelago of the Azores consists of nine islands, Santa Maria, São Miguel, Terceira, Graciosa, São Jorge, Pico, Faial, Flores, and Corvo, and several islets.
    </string>
<!--    <string name="russia_short_details">-->
<!--        Russia is a country about 1.8 times . . .-->
<!--    </string>-->
<!--    <string name="russia_long_details">-->
<!--        Russia is a country about 1.8 times the size of the US occupying the vast area between Europe and the North Pacific Ocean. It has an area of 10, 672,000 sq. miles (17,075,200 sq.km) and a population of almost 150 million people.-->

<!--Occupying a large territory in Europe and Asia Russia is spread over all climatic zones except tropical. It takes over 8 hours by plane to reach from Moscow to Vladivostok on the Pacific coast. West of the Ural mountains from the Black Sea in the South to the Arctic Ocean lies a broad plain with low hills where the historical core of the Russian nation is located. East of the Urals from the border with Kazakhstan, China and Mongolia to the Arctic coast lies Siberia - a scarcely populated area covered by coniferous forest, swamps and tundra in the north and mountainous terrain in the south.-->

<!--The country possesses a wide array of natural resources including major deposits of oil, coal, natural gas, many strategic minerals, diamonds and timber. The economic zone along the 23,533 mile (37,653 km) long coastline (Arctic and Pacific Oceans, Baltic, Black and Caspian Seas) holds significant reserves of fish and oil and natural gas on the sea shelf. Most of the country has a so called harsh continental climate characterized by a big difference between summer and winter temperatures (it gets indeed very cold in Siberia during winter, but it is also very hot in the summer). Russia's geographical location presents a significant obstacle to development - dry or cold climate, terrain, distance and remote location from major sea lanes, all these factors contribute to the situation when large parts of the country have almost no population and development. Russia has only 8% of arable land.-->
<!--    </string>-->
<!--    <string name="srilanka_short_details">-->
<!--        The history of Sri Lanka is unique because . . .-->
<!--    </string>-->
<!--    <string name="srilanka_long_details">-->
<!--        The history of Sri Lanka is unique because the relevance and richness of it extends beyond the areas of South Asia, Southeast Asia and the Indian Ocean. The early human remains which were found on the island of Sri Lanka date back to about 38,000 years ago (Balangoda Man).-->

<!--The historical period roughly begins in the 3rd century CE, based on Pali chronicles like the Mahavamsa, the Deepavamsa, and the Culavamsa.[1] They describe the history of Sri Lanka since the arrival of Prince Vijaya who was from Northern India[2][3][4][5] The earliest documents of settlement in the Island are found in these chronicles. These chronicles cover the period since the establishment of the Kingdom of Tambapanni in the 6th century BCE by the earliest ancestors of the Sinhalese. The first Sri Lankan ruler of the Anuradhapura Kingdom, Pandukabhaya, is recorded for the 4th century BCE. Buddhism was introduced in the 3rd century BCE by Arhath Mahinda (son of the Indian emperor Ashoka).-->

<!--The island was divided into numerous kingdoms over the following centuries, intermittently (between CE 993–1077) united under Chola rule. Sri Lanka was ruled by 181 monarchs from the Anuradhapura to Kandy periods.[6][unreliable source?] From the 16th century, some coastal areas of the country were also controlled by the Portuguese, Dutch and British. Between 1597 and 1658, a substantial part of the island was under Portuguese rule. The Portuguese lost their possessions in Ceylon due to Dutch intervention in the Eighty Years' War. Following the Kandyan Wars, the island was united under British rule in 1815. Armed uprisings against the British took place in 1818 Uva Rebellion and 1848 Matale Rebellion. Independence was finally granted in 1948 but the country remained a Dominion of the British Empire until 1972.-->

<!--In 1972, Sri Lanka assumed the status of a Republic. A constitution was introduced in 1978 which made the Executive President the head of state. The Sri Lankan Civil War began in 1983, including Insurrections in 1971 and 1987, with the 25-year-long civil war ending in 2009. There was an attempted coup in 1962 against the government under Sirimavo Bandaranaike.-->
<!--    </string>-->
    <string name="united_states_short_details">
 Destination USA, a Nations Online Project coun . . .
    </string>
    <string name="united_states_long_details">
    Destination USA, a Nations Online Project country profile of the United States of America, a nation of 50 states, covering the central part of North America.
The Continental United States is bordered by the Atlantic Ocean in the east and the Pacific Ocean in the west. Alaska, the largest US state, occupies a huge peninsula in the extreme northwest of North America. The US state of Hawaii is an island group located in the central Pacific Ocean, southwest of the continental United States.


The USA borders Canada in the north; its southern 3,155 km long border to Mexico is partly furnished with a great wall (or fence). The United States also shares maritime borders with the Bahamas, Cuba, and Russia.

With an area of 9,833,516 km², the USA is the third-largest country in the world. The country is more than twice the size of the European Union or about slightly more than half the size of Russia.

The United States has a population of 330 million people, (in 2021); it is the most populous country in all of the Americas. Its capital is Washington D.C., formally the District of Columbia. The largest US city is New York. Spoken languages are English 80%, and Spanish 13%.
        jeans, hamburger, Bourbon whiskey, Ford, Tesla, Edison, Harley-Davidson, the dollar ($)
cowboys and indians, mustangs, country music, Johnny Cash, Elvis and rock and roll, Blues, Jazz,
New Orleans, the Statue of Liberty, New York City, the Empire State Building, Broadway theatre, Hollywood,
Niagara Falls, Monument Valley, the Grand Canyon, Napa Valley, Aspen, Lake Tahoe, Las Vegas, Florida, California, the Golden Gate Bridge, Marilyn Monroe, Walt Disney, Andy Warhol, Timothy Leary, Batman, Microsoft, Apple, IBM, Google, hot dogs and donuts, diners, Television, soap operas, baseball, football and other college sports, yellow school buses, Star Trek, NASA and the Moon landing, John F. Kennedy, Martin Luther King, Jr., BLM, the FBI and CIA,
John Wayne, rednecks, orthodox evangelicals, everybody has a gun, freemason symbols, creationism,
the American president, the Peanuts, barbie dolls, Kodak film, Miami and San Francisco, Indian Summer, bald eagles, the Hard Rock Cafe, The Blues Brothers, cornflakes and popcorn, Campbell soups, Heinz Tomato Ketchup, Pepsi and Coca Cola.
    </string>
</resources>